// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the chairman of IEBC?",
    answer: "Wafula Chebukati",
    options: [
      "Raila Odinga",
      "William Ruto",
      "Wafula Chebukati",
      "Uhuru Kenyatta"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The parliament of Kenya consists of how many houses?",
    answer: "two",
    options: [
      "one",
      "two",
      "three",
      "four"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The national assembly consists of how many members?",
    answer: "three hundred and fifty",
    options: [
      "two hundred and ninety",
      "fourty seven",
      "three hundred and fifty",
      "four hundred"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many women representatives are there in the national assembly?",
    answer: "forty seven",
    options: [
      "forty seven",
      "forty eight",
      "forty nine",
      "two hundred"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The national assembly consists of how many members?",
    answer: "67",
    options: [
      "47",
      "48",
      "290",
      "67"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Why should I vote?",
    answer: "Because it's my duty to choose the right leaders.",
    options: [
      "Because I have a voters card",
      "Because it's my duty to choose the right leaders.",
      "Because its happens every 5 years",
      "Because I am told to."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who should I Vote for?",
    answer: "Most Qualified Candidate",
    options: [
      "Most popular candidate",
      "Most Qualified Candidate",
      "Most Popular Party",
      "My tribesman"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: " If the president dies, who will succeed him?",
    answer: "Deputy President",
    options: [
      "Leader of the Opposition",
      "Deputy President",
      "Speaker ",
      "Attorney General"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "How many presidential candidates are contesting in the 2022 general elections?",
    answer: "Over Forty",
    options: [
      "Two Only",
      "Over Forty",
      "Three Only",
      "Less than Ten"
    ]
  },

  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];